CHI-JUI WU

Wanrong Junior High School 1 Changqiao Road, Fenglin Town Hualien County 975, Taiwan Website http://chijuiwu.space
Email chijui@chijuiwu.space
GitHub @cjw-charleswu

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are within Human Computer Interaction and Artificial Intelligence, including sensing technologies, mobile devices, ubiquitous computing, proxemic interaction, and machine learning. I build novel supporting toolkits for group collaborations and multi-device interactions, and leverage machine intelligence to enhance existing sensing capabilities within interactive spaces. Recently, I have developed a new tracking infrastructure that enables HCI researchers to build and evaluate proxemic-aware, activity and device-centric interfaces. In my further research, I would like to design and build new cross-device interactions to support ad-hoc individual and group work in public (office) and private (home) spaces.

EDUCATION

MRes. Computational Statistics and Machine Learning, Distinction

2015 - 2016

University College London, UK

Supervisors: Prof. Nicolai Marguardt, Prof. Steven Houben

BSc. Computer Science, First-Class Honours

2011 - 2015

University of St Andrews, UK Supervisor: Prof. David Harris-Birtill

PUBLICATIONS

- [C.1] Wu, CJ., Houben, S., Marquardt, N. <u>2017</u>. EagleSense: Tracking People and Devices in Interactive Spaces using Real-Time Top-View Depth-Sensing. To appear In *Proceedings of the 35th Annual ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems* (Denver, Colorado, USA, May 6 - 11, 2017). CHI '17. ACM, New York, NY.
- [J.1] Wu, CJ., Quigley, A., Harris-Birtill, D. <u>2016</u>. Out of Sight: A Toolkit for Tracking Occluded Human Joint Positions. In *Personal and Ubiquitous Computing*, 21(1), 125-135. Springer London.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

Research Intern, University of St Andrews, UK

June 2015 – September 2015

Explored novel system infrastructures for software recomputation (recomputation.org). Developed a web application to automatically build and run computer programs using virtual

machines and continuous integration tools.

Research Intern, University of St Andrews, UK

Supervisor: Prof. Ian Gent

Investigated interactions between depth-sensing information visualization and user's ability to detect visual notifications and awareness of other surrounding users. Designed and conducted individual and group user studies with the interfaces developed.

Supervisors: Prof. Aaron Quigley, Prof. Per Ola Kristensson

June 2014 – September 2014

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

English Teaching Assistant, Wanrong Junior High School, Hualien, Taiwan

January 2017 -

Teaching in remote rural areas in Taiwan as substitute (mandatory) military service

Present

Mathematics and Chemistry (high school), Computer Science (undergraduate and graduate),

2010 – Present

English Writing (non-native speakers)

AWARDS

Personal Tutor

Honourable Mention, University College London Data Science Student Challenge, UK

February 2016

Best Use of Mendeley API, Hack Cambridge, UK
Dean's List, University of St Andrews, UK
Dean's List, University of St Andrews, UK
Finalist, Barclays Openminds Hackathon, UK
Winner, J.P. Morgan Code for Good Challenge, UK

January 2016 June 2015 June 2014 November 2013 November 2013

SKILLS

Programming

Java, Python, C, C++, C#, Matlab, JavaScript, Go

User Interface

Swing, JavaFX, WinForms, WPF

Hardware

Microsoft Kinect, Phidget, Arduino

Computer Vision (OpenCV), Machine Learning (Scikit-Learn, Keras, XGBoost), Scientific Computing (Numpy, Scipy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn), Information Visualization (D3.js), Graphics (WebGL), Mobile (Android), Web Front-End (Markdown, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery), Web Back-End (Flask, Tornado, Django), Game (Unreal, Phaser, pixi.js), Version Control (Git, TravisCl), Word Processing (LaTeX), Operating System (UNIX), Virtual Machine, Container (Vagrant, Docker)

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITIES

Treasurer, University of St Andrews Computing Society, UK	2014 – 2015
Secretary, University of St Andrews Psychology Society, UK	2013 – 2014
Events Coordinator, University of St Andrews Psychology Society, UK	2012 – 2013
First-year Rep, University of St Andrews Breakaway (Hill-Walking) Society, UK	2011 – 2011